{
    "id": "e8ed482363ba44b28e1835cbd9e8a2fd",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "While I was going home last evening, I .................................. a friend of mine.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "meet",
                "met",
                "had met"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3340ae306ef24786a22bffd919ba17d0"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ..................................... for me at a bus station hoping that I would reach there before 6 pm.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "waited",
                "was waiting",
                "had waited"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7debeb27e8754e6d8f4ab50aa53eb29b"
        },
        {
            "question": "My friend Mr. Gupta .................................... a famous writer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "has",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b5f431e4983349378260ed88a4b065c4"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ....................................... short stories and plays.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "writes",
                "write",
                "writing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ec8f49cdcd634e1caebdf32069d6f072"
        },
        {
            "question": "He .......................................... an anthology of poems too.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has published",
                "publishing",
                "publishes",
                "has publishing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4278f28fa76144728cd7d4e45dfa38c1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Now he says that he ........................................... on a novel.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "works",
                "is working",
                "has worked"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "563a40a8af004f069b4a54fc9ba6a487"
        },
        {
            "question": "Raju ..................................... here yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "came",
                "has come",
                "comes"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "67567e451a0a4cb9872e571f28d15cb9"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ...................................... for Chennai tomorrow.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will leave",
                "would leave",
                "left"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "da24a1d4a2ff488a9781e17acba232cb"
        },
        {
            "question": "I .................................... computer programming now.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "learn",
                "am learning",
                "learning"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "58fd4cba131345f889c2a6497a8bbf9c"
        },
        {
            "question": "The course ................................... last month.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "begins",
                "has begun",
                "began"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "dfee71c5e5d544ac9a6cfd5f259cf0c0"
        }
    ]
}